BGM
It's time for the Goo Goo Channel!
Let's see where we are this time!
This time, we are near the Wakino Art Factory in Kitakyushu City.
Near a fireworks factory called Wakino Art Factory in Kitakyushu City, Kitakyushu Prefecture.
Fireworks factory and
This is my first time to visit a fireworks factory.
That's right.
This Wakino Art Factory is a company that makes fireworks.
Mr. Wakino Art Factory makes fireworks.
I think we talked about how it would be nice if we could make fireworks.
There was also talk of making your own fireworks.
That's right.
The Nonakada Festival 2023 will be held again this year.
I'm thinking about it now.
I wonder if we could display fireworks from there.
Wouldn't that be great?
I'm thinking about it.
It would be great!
It's true, there are no fireworks shows in Nonakada.
That's true.
No fireworks.
No?
No.
There was talk of fireworks.
I just checked while I was on my way to Gerat.
We can all make some kind of fireworks.
Fireworks.
I'll make it.
FireworksFireworks
Can you make it?
Please make it!
What do you mean, "make"?
What are you going to make?
What do you think?
Five of something...
Five each.
I don't know...
If the Executive Committee decides to raise them, is that okay?
Yes, that's right.
Yes, sir.
Yes. - Yes.
Yes. Yes.
What kind of fireworks fascinate you two?
What kind of fireworks?
Do you like fireworks?
I do.
Because of my profession, I can't help but be attracted to dirty fireworks.
I see.
I'm looking for it.
I think they're beautiful.
I see.
And you, Ai?
I like it.
I haven't seen fireworks this year.I haven't seen any fireworks this year.
I didn't see them.
But I did see a little bit of it.
A little bit.
I thought they were going up.
I saw them in the car in Paris.
I also saw it rising on the bus in Osaka from the train.
So I wanted to see it up close.
I see.
I've seen live broadcasts of fireworks shows on Youtube.
Wow.
Someone drank while watching it.
So you like it a lot?
I like it a lot. That's why there's a commentary.
Like, "This is this firework.
I like the one with the climber.
It's like...
I was like, "Oh, I didn't know there was such a thing.
That's great.
Fireworks talk is a lot of fun, isn't it?
We don't do that.
It's a great view.
It's so high up.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Are you the person in charge?
Yes, of the Art Factory on the side.
My name is Izumi. My name is Izumi.
Pleased to meet you.
How long have you been doing this?
I mean, how long have you been in business?
We've been in business for 69 years this year.
69 years!
That's amazing.
About this time...
It will be held in November
at the Munakata Festival
Fireworks to be shot off at the Munakata Festival in November.
for the Munakata Festival in November.
For the Munakata Festival in November.
That's sudden.
I see.
We'd be happy to listen to it with you.
You don't know what you're talking about.
That's right.
While you're teaching us.
Just now...
I was just talking...
You like all kinds of fireworks.
I see you like them.
Climbing the highest peak.
Do you climb?
You're the only one who knows how to do it.
I'm afraid I can't do it this time.
I can't.
That's what it's commonly called.Generally speaking
large ball No. 7
black fried flower
with natural oil or something like that.
If I do it, I'll do
I'm going to do it in natural oil.
I mean with a climbing pole.
big fireworks, usually from size 7 and up.
There are certain sizes.
on a large sized one.
attached as an accessory
of a firework ball.
Separate from the firework balls.
The name of the accessory is collectively
with a climbing pole.
This time
I'm going to launch
a relatively small firework
about 9cm in diameter.
Nine centimeters in diameter.
Is that really going to go off?
This is what's going to go off?
Yes, this is what goes off.
Yes, when it goes off.
This is it?
Not the 9 centimeters.
The original gunpowder charge.
You can't see it. Nine centimeters.
That's right.
When a 9-centimeter firework opens in the sky...When a 9cm firework opens in the sky
It's about 80 meters high.
That's a big one.
Good, because it's big.
And...
We're called the Batten Girls.
Batten.
Can you do that?
It's like an X.
It's difficult.
Fireworks are like circles.
In a circle.
Fireworks.
from the center of the circle.
It's relatively difficult to make a straight line.
huh?
Inside the circle...
Can you make a batch or something?
No, a circle.
Like a map symbol.
Right.
Yes, that's right.
Here are the fireworks.
I'm nervous.
Yes, please.
Oh, what's that?
Are you saving this?Are you saving this?
No, I'm not.
I'm making it.
Cool.
I'm glad.
Take off your shoes.
Yes, of course
It's like this.
It's so cozy, it's like...
It's like...
Like a rushing sound.
I thought it would be more like a rush.
Yes, it is.
Like this, where the craftspeople sit?
Yes, he's actually making fireworks.
This is...
He weakens the gunpowder.
And when they're combined, they make fireworks.
Amazing.
So it depends on how you put it in this weak?
Yes, it depends on how you put it inside.
It depends on how you put it in.
It's a matter of taste.
Yes, it does. What about those who are really good with their hands?
Clumsy.
Clumsy, clumsy.
Are you clumsy?
A little.
I'm sure I'm good at cooking.
I just remembered... at this moment... it's okay to forget. I just remembered, and it's okay if you forgot at this point.
They say if you catch a millimeter of fish, you can catch 10 meters.
I see.
We talked about it.
It's getting like 80 meters in the night sky.
The walking error is already settled by how many meters in the night sky.
Have you made one before, Mr. Nizumi? I have.
It's my first one.
Is this your first one?
Yes, do you remember?
Yes, I remember my first piece.
How long ago was it?
About three years ago.
I didn't know that was possible.
You put a lot of thought into the fireworks, don't you?
Past relationships, you know.
No, I named my child beautifully.
I see.
You gave him a name?
No, not the name, but for the fireworks.
For the fireworks, for this fireworks, I named a sentence after my child's name.
That's nice.
Emo, emo, emo.
What would you name it next?
Trunks.
I'm not addicted to it.
It's not something I'd shoot up.
I'll try it while I'm sitting down.
Yes, please.Yes, thank you very much.
A basic round firework is something like this.
You can do it with your hands like this?
You hold it down in the middle with this.
This is basically called a button.
It's a round floral hair.
If you take the middle out, it's like this.
Why isn't it falling down?
You're clawing it.
Here.
Line this side up, too.
If you put them together, you end up with a nice, round flower hair.
You'll end up with a nice, round flower hair.
What?
The colors and the clothes.
I'd like you to arrange them in the way you want to make them.
If you can arrange them in the way you want to make them
You'll have a round flower hair.
You just stuff them in there.
Seven circles, you mean.
As it is now, if I arrange them the way I did...
I'd only have circles.
But this...
Just to make it open.
And put in a spice.
I've already put it in.
If this becomes a Niko-chan mark, it will be
This is Niko-chan.
You can draw a smiley face here?
Yes, just like you said. Yes, you're right.
A stylish side dish.
And a mouth... and if the color changes...
I'll put some eyes in there.
Wow! That's how it's done!
I'm a little impressed. Wow!
It's not hard to make dragon balls.
A star?
It's not hard to make a cross in the middle like this.
It's not hard to do.
I'll give it a try.
That's a good idea.
So the point is, if I make the face of the star look like a star...
I can make it look like a star?
If it works.
Oh, you can't? You're thinking hard.
Is it difficult to make a star?
Maybe.
It opens up in the middle.
The more it's on the inside, the harder it is to fly.
It's kind of hard to spread out.
That's why the stars are so small.
Maybe it's just a big mess.
Or they'll come out.
I see.
I wonder...
It's a beautiful firework.
Only three of them.
Some amateur.
I'll make it easy for you. Let's make it easy to understand.
Let's make it easy to understand.
Yes, sir.
huh?
On the other hand, let's say the first three shots...
You're right.
You explained it before, right?
Yes.
I didn't even warn you.
Hmm?
Maybe we should ask the MC to come in.
That's true.
Amateur fireworks challenge corner.
If we do it like that...
It would lower the bar.
There's green and red.
Red is red, right?
Red and green.
Three colors now.
Orange
Dragon Ball
It's on Mr. Fujimoto's screen.
So I guess it's red around it, orange in the middle.
Right.
It's backwards. It's backwards.
Dragon Ball in red with orange around it.Dragon Ball with orange around and red inside
I'll make it.
Or, well, if it's a few decimal columns or something, then just poof!
Oh!
That's a good point.
You know what you're talking about.
I like the idea of a numeral pillar.
I don't know, maybe a letter from my name.
Oh, no.
It's a bad idea.
No, no, no, no, no.
Three letters?
R for RRRRRR...
R is RRRR
There...
It's Mr. Fujimoto
Fujimoto-san's uncialized character
Mr. Fujimoto's intangible character
If it's the Niowa Center
I'll tell you about it.
Imo (sweet potato)
sweet potato
But...
I can do it.
Yes.
Green
Green.
Definitely.
A leaf or something.A leaf or something.
I don't know what it is, green.
what about once?
But a batten
Butten
But batten is hard to do.
I've heard the same thing over and over again
Let's try batten.
The same thing.
You're right.
Does the one on the bottom come out in the middle, color-wise?
No, let's see...
The bottom one.
What?
No, outside, right?
I mean, here and here.
Outside, outside, right?
The more outside, the more outside.
No, it's...
No, it's not.
No...
This way.
When it goes up, it spins like a baseball. Like a firework spins.
So you don't understand shuffles? I don't know where they go up.
What? So if you put red in here and green in here and blue in here, if you open it up like this...
If I put red in here and green in here and blue in here, it will look like red is mixed with various colors, or if I open it like this, it will look like a beautiful tier.
It's difficult, isn't it?
There is also luck.
When you raise itWhen you raise it.
It's not just with your hands.
You throw down.
How do you do it?
I thought I could control it that way.
You should try it... throwing down and up with your nose.
That's what I'm going to do.
I can't be bothered.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's mainstream.
It's simple, and I like the color.
And I'll keep in mind that the difference of one millimeter is 10 meters.
If we use two colors, I think we can divide it up pretty nicely, if we separate this one and that one.
I see.
In that case, we'll split them this way and that way.
So you're going to pack both?
I'll fill them both.
We'll fill both of the circles.
I'll stuff both, so that a circle and a half circle and a half circle will make a beautiful circle.
If you are hungry, if you are hungry, if you are hungry,
Then it can be a watermelon? If you cut it in half.
Oh, really?
What is it? What is it? What is it?
You want to... make watermelon?
I have made watermelons before.
Have you?
Is that a mistake?
Maybe it's a little bit of a save-victorian.
Yes, I think so. Watermelon, yes.
How was it? How did it go?
It just seemed to come out okay.
It came out?
Well, I'm gonna stop. Do you want some of that?
Watermelon?
Watermelon...I said so myself.
Batteries?
Battery?
Were the seeds black?
I didn't make the seeds. No wonder.
No, no, no, no, no. We're doing a watermelon version.
Okay, that's enough. Watermelon pit.
Let's do it. Let's do it. I'm curious, I'm curious.
Let's do it.
Please.
I will make boten.
I would like to make a few dragon ball brass.
I would like to make orthodox buttons.
Yes, let's start.
Is this it!
Yes.
Next,
Give it to me for Oden.
Like this.
On this side,
Yes.
Please put it all in.
Can you give me this? Can you give me this?
Not yet.
I'm sorry.
This is rice husk, too.
What?
I'll sprinkle it on quickly.
I see.
Rice after threshing.
That's all right.
Is it okay?
It's difficult.
Put them two by two.
I see.
Okay, and then can I put them in the engine and put them in the front?
Yes, sir. Oh, great.
Like this.
Okay. Now tap the top a little bit.
Slowly.
Let's go a little more.
Where there's a little gap...
Pull it in like this.
Pull it in a little bit like this.
Make a gap and put it there.
There you go.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Close it.
Yes, sir.
And...
I showed you something, didn't I?I could show you a few things.
Here, take this.
Here.
Does it look too hard?
Wrap it around.
It's really tough.
Tough.
I'm a little impressed.
You still have a lot of work to do here, don't you?
Yes, sir.
It's not enough here, either.
Yes, it is.
Heh.
So, here's the cut.
It's quite fine.
Type A?
No, sir.
No?
Type A?
Good. I wish I could.
And if it's flattening out...
Is it flat?
Let's put a little more in.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
So, I'm going to open it up one more time, and I'm going to do this for you.So I'm gonna open it up again, and I'm gonna do it a little bit like this.
What?
And now, let's unravel it one more time.
On top of this?
Yes, sir.
That's fine.
This one looks hard.
Half of this should do it.
What?
This is it?
The fire starts here, goes all the way to the middle.
Then the fire comes out here, ignites this powder, and goes bang.
It's the exact same procedure.
Is that why there's a hole in it?
That's right.
That's it.
It's a hole for the fuse.
Here.
Put this can here.
Tomp, tomp, tomp, tomp
Knock, knock.
Have them take it out.
Like this.
Put this paper
Now...
Now that side.
Okay. - Okay.
You want to go here?
I have to drill a hole.
I see.I see.
In that case...
I'll make a hole.
You want me to stick it in already?
Oh, my God.
If you stick it in here slowly, it'll fall apart.
Here you go.
Now, we're going to put these two cups together as one.
If it's out of alignment, that's the end of it.
Here we go. Ready?
Ha! It's so hard!
Did you get it?
No, it didn't!
This is the real game!
Just barely finished
I'm just about done
Laughter
That's great!
You did okay.
To a point.
That's great!
That's important.
The trick is...
Sleeve.
I close it.
And if you don't have enough firmness...
When you shake it like this, it makes a sound.
You'll hear a sound.Sound.
Reverse it.
Like kara-kara-kara already.
I can put it in again.
That's a lot of work, too.
Not this much.
I don't know how many times I've done it.
Oh, yeah!
Before I forget.
It's red.
Red.
Fireworks are called Benny.
I want to say Benny too!
Here.
I'm going to have them put it right into the stand.
Oh...
I just put it in the table.
e
hmm.
Because fine and fine medicine are not compatible with each other.
They don't go well together.
So I'm going to put a divider in there for you
so that they don't mix.
In
Tinel?
Tinel or tinel
Line them up.
Next one.
This is gonna be so hard.That looks really hard.
It's like this.
Like this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Just give a little snap here at the edge.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to go forward.
Yes, sir.
Like a part.
That's right, here's the wiener.
Here comes the Cinelli.
Cinelli.
Orange. This is orange.
Now that we have the orange, we need you to cut off the end of the orange.
And then we're going to cut it in half and put one more piece in.
We'll lay them out to make the outline for now.
Yes.
Mr. Hiroshi made this.
Oh, yes. One more year?
One more year.
What?
Do you want me to crumple it up once?
Once crumpled.
Make the paper a little tighter.
Yes, sir.
Heh heh heh.
Oh, erase it.
Let's erase it. Oh, let's turn it off.
Yes, let's turn it off.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Oh, this is good.
I feel very good about this.
Yes, thank you.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Yeah, good.
Kondori.
Perfect. It's like candy.
Yes, it's good.
It doesn't bend, does it? It's bent.
Does it look good? I think it looks good.
The gap is good? Yes, it's fine.
We'll fill in the gaps inside.
I see. Yes.
That's good.
Let's do it together.
Let's see how the bridge looks.
Will it be a nice circle?
Let's do it.
Here we go. Ready?
Here we go.
And here comes the real work.
The real work.
We have to do this.
You're right.
Would you like to practice once? Would you like to practice once?
Of course I will.
I'm not in labor anymore.
So...
That's what I mean.
Oh, wow.
That's right. That's right. That's good.
Very good. Yes.
Oh, yes.
I can do it now. Yes, yes, yes, it's fine.
Yes, can I go?
While you're still feeling it.
Don't be nervous.
Here we go.
Oh, wow.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
But...
Yes, are you okay? Yes
Yes, indeed. I don't think the Dragon Ball side is collapsing.
Yes, it is.
Go from the other side.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hm...
Hm?
Is he okay?
I don't know.
Well, sometimes...
No, you seem okay.No, it looks fine.
Oh, are you okay?
I'm on comms. You're here. You're here.
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
Wow, hey.
I thought I could make it.
All right.
Chain of forgetfulness.
Yes, sir.
If it's that bad.
Do I have to spill it?
You have to spill it.
Just a little.
Yes, sir.
Please stop.
Don't be scared.
With both hands.
It's red.
Yes, sir.
It's red!
You're freaked out.
I'm scared.
You're freaking me out.
Oh, my God.
I'm in the red, too.
Can I ask her the same question?
It's a festival red.
Why do you call him Benny?
That's funny.
Scary.Scary.
You look good.
Here you go.
Is it good?
Spin it.
Yo!
How's that?
How's this?
(Laughs)
Laughing.
What's that feeling?
What's that feeling again?
Laughing.
Laughter.
Applause.
What do you think?
I don't know if it's to your liking.
I'm going to go.
Yo!
You want to drink it in one gulp?
Let's just tilt this up until it spills out.
I see.
Now, it's just like this...
Yes!
That's good, isn't it?
Now, if you'll just stand it up...
Third time's the charm.
Beautiful. Beautiful.Beautiful. Beautiful.
Oh, there it is. There it is, Mr. Urawa.
Another one?
Oh, yes.
I see.
I like the craftsmanship of this.
I'll just tape it up.
Yes, sir.
It's really good.
There we go.
Oh, yes.
Should I fill it in?
Yes, sir.
Yes, indeed.
It's such a big job.
It looks like.
Yes, it's OK.
Finally, for the third time.
I don't want to launch again.
I've got a lot of feelings for you.
Now that we've made it...
It's better to launch all the time.
And then there's the hardest part.
You're in charge of the batten.
I don't know what I'll do.
We'll make batten.
We're going to make sausages.
The sausage is the part where you roll it up?
That's right.
But we'll push on the hips.I do push the hips, though.
I put it in once.
Yes, I'll push.
Oh, I'm going into the ocean.
Oh, really.
Seven pieces are ready.
Rolling it up...
Eiko, it's so hard!
Oh, wow!
30 seconds.
Is this the same as Mr. Fujimoto's?
But it's a sausage.
Oh, yes, it's a sausage.
Sausage.
Sausage?
Oh, so they're the same.
So we have both sausage and sticky rice?
Oh, I see.
Three sausages.
Okay, three pieces now.
Oh, it's light.
I can put them on top of this, right?
One. Two.
That's a cute signal.
Nine.
Here we go. 9.
A little bit.
It's a little too wrinkled.
I'm sorry. I'll try one more time.Sorry. I'll try one more time.
I feel like I was pretty forceful just now.
Yes, it was.
I'm sorry.
Okay, take your time.
Slowly. Okay.
Can I do it this way?
Goal. There you go.
And then..,
It's going to be a little bit...
Skew.
I have to tighten it up,
I don't know,
It's going to slip off.
It's beautiful.
It is indeed beautiful.
It really looks like a wiener.
Yes, it is.
It's different.
I didn't realize how hard it is. I knew it.
Yes, it's OK.
Oh.
Finally, the third time.
Yes.
Ho.
May I? Yes! OK!
Oh, it's done!
Is it done?
Well, it's coming along very nicely. Here.
Here it is, yes. This is the place, yes.
I see, I'm a little off. Thank you very much.
That's great. Wow! It's so beautiful. Amazing.
Yes, thank you very much.
Does it look good?
Thank you very much.
Here we go.
This is a little bit more exciting.
Yes, it's a little bit up in the air.
To be honest, I'd like to see you fail at least once.
If I'm the only one who fails, I'm the lame one.
I'm just trying to show you how hard it is.
I want you to fail at least once.
That's luck, right?
I wonder if I'll be able to do that work right away.
Wasn't it packed like that?
I don't know...
We'll match it here.
You can go as far as you want.
If you do too much here, it'll fall apart.
I think this is as close as we can get.
And then...
If you do it like this, it will fall apart.
No, I'm scared.
It's like Mr. Fujimoto, isn't it?
I'll end up like Mr. Fujimoto.
And you don't have to say it.
A little more?
Not yet.
That's about right. That's about it.
Yes, sir.
Wow, that's a lot of work.
Here we go.
Ready, ready, ready.
Oh!
Yum!
Yes!
But it's so hard.
Yum!
It's so good!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I thought it would be good to move it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Stick with one of those.
What?
From here to here.
I'll let you hold it.
It didn't make a sound.
It was like a capo.
Even when it was zinging.
By hand.
You were so good.
I've never worked harder.
What's this for?
It's a little bit like...
It's like, uh, blending a chemical.
Uh...
And now...And now, I'm already there.
I'm making sure that the mesh is properly aligned, so...
Yes, sir.
Now all that's left to do is
I'll take the tail.
We're still here.
That felt good.
All of it. All of it.
To the next level.
Oh.
Yes, sir.
Bup, bup, bup in green.
This one, this one.
I got it! Ein!
It's done!
Yes, it was!
Okay, everyone, that's it for today's original fireworks.
Thank you very much.
What's going on?
There's one more step.
What's that?
We're going to put make-up on the fireworks.
It's called "balling".
Kraft paper, like cardboard, is put on top.Kraft paper, which is like the raw material for cardboard, is stretched over the top.
Then, pressure is applied to the paper to make it open evenly.
That's as good as it gets.
When it's finally finished...
If we launch it as it is now, it will spread out from the green line, and it won't have a beautiful circumference, so we're working on it now so that it will open up nicely.
So we have to do one more process now to make it open up nicely.
This will take about a week for a piece this size.
A week?
Yes, sir.
Only in the spring?
Very much so.
So we'll take responsibility for that.
I see.
We'll take care of it.
Thank you very much.
If you want, you can have the inside cleaned up a little.
Can you do that?
If you want.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, I can.
So in November
Yes
Sometimes
Sometimes your fireworks
I can't wait to see them.
I'm looking forward to this. I'm looking forward to this.
I'm looking forward to it.
But since you've come to our company...
Yes.
We're actually going to shoot off some fireworks, if you don't mind.
Okay?
You mean I can see them?
Yes, sir.
With your original colors?
Red and green.
Blue, Mr. Fujimoto?
Blue is fine.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to launch it.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Excellent.
I want to take care of you.
I'm done. It looks like you made it.
How was it? It was fun.
What is it? What is it? I thought you two were really good at it.
You were amazing. You're so good.
I learned a lot from watching you.
It felt so good. It was so smooth.
It was like a craft. It's a valuable experience.
I've been working on it for a while now. We've been putting a lot of strings together.
They've prepared something for us, right?
They're showing us a trial.
So we'll wait until sunset.
Let's wait until sunset and look for bugs.
I'm always looking for bugs. It's a habit.
Ever since we went on location, it's a habit.
There are a lot of them around here. I'm sure they'll be here soon.
So they'll be here soon? I'll keep an eye out for them.
Okay. I'll just wait for the sunset.
I'll wait for sunset.
I'll wait.
Thank you for watching.
Now, the sun has completely set.
It is, isn't it? It's dark.
What do you think? Izumi, are you ready for the fireworks?
Yes, they're ready.
Already.
Amazing.
Yes, they are ready to be launched.
Where are the fireworks going to be?
This one is over there.
Oh, it's pretty close.
It's pretty close.
How many rounds are there?
Well, there will be 10 rounds today.
Ten?
Yes, 10.
That's great.Excellent.
Okay, so can we start about five seconds before now?
Yes, five seconds ago is fine.
Can I go now?
Oh, does this sound the same?
It's fine.
Oh, I can do it. Great.
Ready.
Five, four, three, two, one, zero.
Wow, that was amazing.
It's close.
Wow, close.
That was amazing.
It's amazing.
It's so close.
Red.
Amazing.
That's great.
What? It's right below us.
Oh, no, it's so low.
Blue. Blue. Blue.
Green. Green.
Green.
Oh, it's right above us.
Oh, my gosh.
That's great. Closer and closer.
Pink.
Oh, this is it.
This is it.It's amazing.
It's amazing.
Amazing.
Oh, what's that? Is it a face?
It's a smiley face.
Amazing. I see.
That's amazing. It's so close.
Wow, it's so close. Fall, fall, fall!
Oh, wow!
So close. Falling, falling, falling!
Oh, my God!
That's great!
Oh, my God! That's great!
Look, they're so angry.
So close.
Oh, my gosh!
It's so big!
I bet the boys who were just playing baseball are overjoyed.
Something fell!
What? It's definitely coming down.
What is it?
Isn't that it?
Look! We packed it.
The debris!
That's why we're so close.
The wind was just blowing this way.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Wow!
I didn't know it had this wind on it.
It's coming apart.
That's great!
Thank you very much.
So, now that we've seen the fireworks...
This is actually going to be launched at the Munakata Festival.
So we have to think about how the fireworks will be composed.
Well, you know, we said something about us producing them.
I see, I had already said that.
The members, of course, are all students and PET bottles!
Yay! We'll work together with the students to come up with some ideas.
Oh, I see, with everyone!
I'm sure that the local people will be interested in how the fireworks will be set off at the end.
We have less than two months to go.
We don't have that much time left.
Yes, it's about two months, but we're still working on it.
I hope you are looking forward to seeing what kind of fireworks will be displayed at the show.
I'm looking forward to seeing the fireworks.
So, as you can see...
The Google channel will be on November 3 to 5.
I, R.FUJIMOTO and
Batten Girls
will be playing a central role in the filming and uploading to YouTube from time to time.
Oh, fun!
Yes, it is!
And of course, we would like to hear from you, our viewers, through your comments.
I would like to refer to your opinions through the comments.
Yes, sir.
So, thank you very much for your time today!So, thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.